

1507 137th Avenue | San Leandro, CA 94578 | 510.593.8403

Personal Website: kevin0920.github.io | kevinlingsike@gmail.com

U.S Citizen

Innovative, energetic and motivated, full stack, front to backend software engineer with extensive training in software development in programming languages, applications and protocols across several platforms eagerly seeks learning challenges with functional-design team to produce outstanding products. Highly reliable and confident professional.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Languages:HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, JavaBackend:Django, Node.js, Express.js, Flask, MongooseDatabases:MySQL, MongoDB, FireStoreFrameworks:Flask, Django, Node.JS, Angular 4, React.JS

Libraries: JQuery, Bootstrap, Materialize, Font-Awesome Architecture: OOP, REST

Web Tech: HTTP, TCP/IP, AJAX, API Miscellaneous: Git, AWS, Heroku, Adobe Photoshop

PROJECTS

Place order Website: built in MEAN framework which uses Mongodb as database, angular4, Google login API, Google Map API, Bootstrap, Express, Socket.io, Node.JS, jQuery, HTML, CSS. The first account will be the website admin can create menu in detail. The future users can either choose google social login or regular login to placing orders, then when the order submitted, will receive confirmation emails with order detail and total amount of the purchase. For user experience, there is total online user section and total order history for related account, and people can like the specific food they might purchase again.
 Source code: https://github.com/Kevin0920/food-copy
 Deploy link: https://pure-fortress-43994.herokuapp.com/

Booking Events: MEAN Frame work, login users can create different events will separate by different states with CRUD
(Create, Read, Update and Delete) feature, people can join the event and post comments to the specific event, and can cancel
joining status. Event can create edit or delete event. In addition, for user interface design purpose also set Google Map API
image down in the footer section.

• **Q&A/Market Trading Space:** MEAN framework, users post questions for people answering, and keep tracking and counting the total number of answers. Also, people can like the answers. Another feature is making posts for selling products with listing the detail of products. Products with their images and detail in home page randomly displaying as slide show.

Source code: https://github.com/Kevin0920/Market Deploy link: https://young-basin-45853.herokuapp.com/

• Course Enrollment: Implement in CRUD used Mongodb as database, angular4, Bootstrap, Express, Node.JS, jQuery, HTML, CSS. Students can enroll any courses and display course and personal detail. At the meantime, student can delete the course they do not wish to participate.

Source code: https://github.com/Kevin0920/courseEnroll Deploy link: https://ancient-inlet-75992.herokuapp.com/

EXPERIENCE

Graphic Design Assistant, Duxwell Printing, (San Francisco, CA), July 2016 – April 2017

Provided timely, detailed, and personalized custom printing and graphics design, consultation, typography and printing services with Adobe's InDesign and Photoshop. Produced brochures, business cards, booklets, labels and flyers for numerous brands. Effectively managed daily operations; Assigned personnel according to required tasks.

Marketing/Product Support, Shaklee Corp. (Pleasanton, CA), Oct 2015 – July 2016 Extended superb reception and administrative services including call management to address customer needs and achieve customer satisfaction. Accurately rendered complete details of the Shaklee Compensation Plan to include specific bonus- qualification rules and volume requirements for all Shaklee distributors.

IT Support (Intern), California Nurses Association (Oakland, CA), Jan 2012 - April 2012

Managed computer hardware system to run services for network users; installed, updated, configured and monitored account bookings and system for company supplies. Processed requests and delivered data to client computers over a local network or the Internet, often configured to handle client service load.

EDUCATION

University of California, Davis, CA, Graduated: 2014

BACHELOR OF ARTS in Economics

Software Engineer, Coding Dojo (Certification), (San Jose, CA), June 2017 – Sep 2017

Coding Bootcamp teaches three full technology stacks in a single 14-week program. Courses involved immersive web development specializing in Front-end and Full Stack fundamentals, enabling comprehensive end to end project management and control. Daily practicing Algorithms for logic thinking and building web apps from scratch to CRUD/RESTFUL environment with useful API. Accomplishment as top 1% students during the period and keep creating new challenge projects after program.